synapseinteractive.com 2011-10-10

# SEO Website, Search Engine Optimization Company India, SEO company India - Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.synapseinteractive.com/) » **Disclaimer**

SynapseIndia is committed to protect the privacy of any personally identifiable data collected for use in this website. The website is administered by SynapseIndia and we want you to feel secure when accessing information on our website.

**An overview of how personally identifiable data is protected**  
SynapseIndia gathers data in two ways: indirectly through our website, and directly, when you fill in information on various pages of SynapseIndia. In this case, we notify you as to why the data is required and how it will be used. It is completely at your discretion whether or not you want to provide the information.

**How personally identifiable information is used by SynapseIndia**  
Information collected by SynapseIndia is thoroughly analyzed so that only the effective data can be identified. This helps us improve the website.

**Sharing of data with third parties**  
SynapseIndia is a global organization and data collected may be transferred internationally through our worldwide organization. We do not sell personally identifiable information. However, in the event that we need to disseminate any individual information, we will notify you, as why we are asking for the data. In any case, you have the full authority to decide whether or not you provide it.

**Sensitive personal data privacy**  
SynapseIndia generally do not seek to collect sensitive data through this website. In case we do, we will ask your consent to your proposed use of the data. Sensitive personal data may be collected incidentally, however, by providing us with unsolicited sensitive personal data, you agree to our usage of the data subject to applicable law described in this privacy statement.

**Sharing of access to your information**  
SynapseIndia gives you full entitlement to know whether we hold information that pertains to you. You also have the right to correct information that may be inaccurate by sending us an e-mail.

**Security of data**  
SynapseIndia takes all necessary steps to maintain security of data on this website. By sharing information on this website, you should understand that Internet is an open architecture and data flow may occur over networks without security measures, and may be accessed or used by people other than those for whom intended.

In short, SynapseIndia is interested in protecting your data. For more queries about our privacy policy, please contact us.
